Nothing will stop them...
Mimic 2 is a horror, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Jean de Segonzac.
Detective Klaski investigates the death and mutilation of three men
and soon crosses paths with Remy, an entomologist.
Soon, he discovers that she is being stalked by a giant
shape-shifting insect who is bent on taking over New York.
Remy Panos, played by Alix Koromzay.
Det. Klaski, played by Bruno Campos.
Sal Aguirre, played by Gaven E. Lucas.
Nicky, played by Will Estes.
Darksuit, played by Edward Albert.
Morrie Deaver, played by Jon Polito.
Mimic 2 is a 2001 science fiction horror film, directed by Jean de Segonzac, with
a script inspired by a short story of the same name by Donald A.
The movie was a direct-to-DVD sequel to Mimic (1997), and
was followed by Mimic 3: Sentinel (2003).
The thriller stars long-time film veteran Edward Albert, along
with Alix Koromzay, Bruno Campos and Jon Polito.
The film explores themes of beach, mutation,
transformation, animal attack, cockroach.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.